Guide to the George W. Wilbur Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
--Correspondence with Susan W. Rice
--Correspondence with Llewellyn Jones
--Correspondence with E. P. Warren
--Correspondence with "Mary"
--Correspondence with Others
--Invitations and Christmas Cards
WILBUR, ELLEN RICE
--Correspondence with Albert H. Wilbur
--Correspondence with Susan W. Rice
--Correspondence with Cornelia Warren
--Correspondence with Others
--Invitations and Greeting Cards
WILBUR, ALBERT H.
--Miscellaneous Correspondence
RICE, SUSAN W.
--Miscellaneous Correspondence
OTHER PERSONAL CORRESPONDENCE
Series II. George W. Wilbur's Professional Papers
CASES: CONTRACT FILES
CASES: LONG TERM INDIVIDUAL CLIENT FILES
--Burke, Michael and Robert L.
--Hulbert, Thomas H.
--Jones, Roswell N.
--Rice, Charlotte and Francis H.
CASES: MINING COMPANY FILES
--Morris Glick and Joseph Ingham vs. Pittsburgh
--Concentrating and Mining Company
--Ruby Chief Mining and Milling Company
CASES: PROBATE FILES
CASES: REAL ESTATE FILES
CASES: STREET IMPROVEMENT FILES
--Paving in Chicago
--Paving in Oak Park
--Paving in other cities
--Sewers, water mains in Chicago
--Sewers, water mains in Oak Park
--Sewers, water mains in West Hammond
--Subway in Chicago
--Miscellaneous
CASES: OTHER CASE FILES
CASES: FRAGMENTS FROM FILES
PROFESSIONAL CORRESPONDENCE
FINANCIAL RECORDS
NOTEBOOKS
PRINTED MATERIAL
Series III. George W. Wilbur's Personal and Business Papers
DIARIES
PERSONAL FINANCIAL RECORDS
--Account books
--Bills and receipts
--Checks (canceled) and check registers
--Housekeeping correspondence
----With Irving Terwilliger (banker)
----With Others
BUSINESS RECORDS
--McLaughlin Smoke Consumer Company
--Milling and mining
--Other Business Papers
WRITINGS
OTHER PAPERS
Series IV. Other Family Papers
COOK AND RICE FAMILY PAPERS
--Cook Family
--Rice Family
----Rice, Francis H. and George H.
----Rice, Susan C. and Mary C.
WILBUR, SARAH ANN COOK
--Financial papers
--Other papers
WILBUR, ELLEN RICE
--Oak Park/Belvidere Property
--Other Personal Business Correspondence
--Other papers
--Printed material
WILBUR, ALBERT H.
RICE, SUSAN W.
JONES, SUSAN WILBUR
--Personal Business Correspondence
--Financial papers
--Other papers
--Printed material
--Scrapbooks
UNIDENTIFIED
Series V. Printed Material
CHURCH PUBLICATIONS
NEWSPAPERS
MISCELLANEOUS
Series VI. Photographs
IDENTIFIED PEOPLE
--Wilbur Family
--Others
UNIDENTIFIED PEOPLE BY PLACE
--California
--Illinois
--Kansas
--Massachusetts
--Michigan
--New York
OTHER PHOTOGRAPHS
Oversize
GEORGE W. WILBUR'S PROFESSIONAL PAPERS
--Cases: Long term individual client files
--Cases: Milling and mining files
--Correspondence
GEORGE W. WILBUR'S PERSONAL AND BUSINESS PAPERS
--Business Records
----Milling and mining
--Other Papers
OTHER FAMILY PAPERS
--Cook and Rice Family Papers
----Rice Family
--Wilbur, Ellen Rice
----Printed material
--Jones, Susan Wilbur
----Financial papers
----Printed material
--Unidentified
PRINTED MATERIAL
--Newspapers
--Miscellaneous
----Advertisements
----Belvidere playbills and announcements
--Restricted Fragile Papers
Civil engineering -- Illinois -- Chicago; Civil engineering -- Illinois -- Oak Park; Industries -- Colorado; Mentally ill women; Mills and mill-work -- Colorado; Mineral industries -- Colorado; Mines and mineral resources -- Colorado; Practice of law -- Illinois; Railroads -- United States -- Employees; Illinois -- History -- 1865-; Illinois -- Social life and customs; Illinois -- Boone County -- Belvidere; West (U.S.) -- Description and travel; Account books -- United States; Cabinet photographs; Visiting cards; Case files -- United States; Cyanotypes (photographic prints); Diaries -- United States; Family papers; Letterpress copybooks; Photographic prints -- United States; Scrapbooks -- United States; Tintypes (prints); Lawyers -- Illinois; Miners -- Colorado; Belvidere Standard (Belvidere, Ill.); College News (Wellesley, Mass.); Jones, Llewellyn, 1884-1961; Jones, Susan Wilbur, 1893-; Wilbur, Albert H. (Albert Harper); Wilbur, George W. (George Willis), 1851-1931; Cook family; Rice family; Wilbur family -- Archives; McLaughlin Smoke Consumer Company; Pittsburgh Concentrating and Mining Company; Ruby Chief Mining and Milling Company; Wellesley College -- Students
- Personal Correspondence, 1807-1954; Series I; 12.25; (31 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Series I, Personal Correspondence, is organized into seven subseries: George W. Wilbur, Sarah Ann Cook Wilbur, Susan Jones Wilbur, Ellen Rice Wilbur, Albert H. Wilbur, Susan W. Rice, and Other Personal Correspondence. Cross-references have been made to reveal all occurrences of each person's correspondence. Undated letters are filed at the end, grouped by address wherever possible.
  - WILBUR, GEORGE W.
    - Correspondence with Sarah Ann Cook Wilbur
      - For Sarah Ann Cook Wilbur's other correspondence, see: folders 421-551
      - Correspondence, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1873-74 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 3-11)
        Letter of [1875? Feb 13] on back of letter from AHW to GWW of same date, and letter of [1875 Sep] on back of letter from AHW to SACW 1875 Sep 6
      - Correspondence, 1876 (Box 1, Folder 12-18)
        2 letters of [1876 Jan] on back of letters from AHW to SACW of 1875 Dec 28 and Dec 30
      - Correspondence, 1877 (Box 2, Folder 19-24)
        Letter of Fri. morning [1877? Dec 14] on back of letter from AHW to SACW of [1877? Dec 6]
      - Correspondence, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 25-33)
      - Correspondence, 1879 Jan-Mar (Box 2, Folder 34-37)
      - Correspondence, 1879 Apr-Dec (Box 3, Folder 38-46)
        Letter of [1879 Aug] on back of letter from AHW to SACW of 1879 Aug 15, and letter of 1879 Oct 27 on back of letter from AHW to GWW of 1879 Oct 19, and letter of 1879 Dec 9 to "My dear children"
      - Correspondence, 1880 Jan-Oct (Box 3, Folder 47-56)
        Letter of 1880 Mar 8 on back of letter from AHW to SACW of 1880 Feb 19
      - Correspondence, 1880 Nov-Dec (Box 4, Folder 57-58)
      - Correspondence, 1881 (Box 4, Folder 59-66)
        Letter of 1881 Jan 24 on back of letter from AHW to GWW of 1880 [i.e. 1881] Jan 16
      - Correspondence, 1882 Jan-Jul (Box 4, Folder 67-73)
      - Correspondence, 1882 Aug-Dec (Box 5, Folder 74-78)
        Letter of [1882 Aug] on back of letter from George W. Cook to GWW of 1882 Aug 28. Also letter of [1882] Sep 16 on back of letter from Sarah A. Cook to SACW of 1882 Sep 14
      - Correspondence, 1883 (Box 5, Folder 79-94)
      - Correspondence, 1884 Jan-Feb (Box 5, Folder 95-97)
      - Correspondence, 1884 Mar-Dec (Box 6, Folder 98-113)
      - Correspondence, 1885 (Box 7, Folder 114-132)
        Letter by SWR to GWW of [1885 Mar 25] on back of letter from SACW to GWW of [1885 Mar 25], and letter of 1885 Dec 13 on back of letter from AHW to SACW of 1885 Dec 7
      - Correspondence, 1886 Jan-Mar (Box 7, Folder 133-135)
        Letter of 1886 Jan 27 on back of letter from AHW to SACW of 1886 Jan 17
      - Correspondence, 1886 Apr-Dec (Box 8, Folder 136-146)
      - Correspondence, 1887 (Box 8, Folder 147-154)
      - Correspondence, 1888 (Box 8, Folder 155-158)
      - Correspondence, 1889 (Box 9, Folder 159-160)
      - Correspondence, 1890 (Box 9, Folder 161-167)
        Letter of [1890] Jun 13 on back of letter from AHW to SACW of 1890 Jun 8
      - Correspondence, 1891 (Box 9, Folder 168-175)
      - Correspondence, 1892 (Box 9, Folder 176)
      - Correspondence, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 177-178)
      - Correspondence, 1894 (Box 9, Folder 179-183)
      - Correspondence, 1895 (Box 10, Folder 184-186)
      - Correspondence, 1896 (Box 10, Folder 187-192)
      - Correspondence, 1897 (Box 10, Folder 193-199)
      - Correspondence, 1898 (Box 10, Folder 200-206)
      - Correspondence, 1899 (Box 10, Folder 207-212)
        Letter of 1899 Oct 2 on back of letter from Addie Cook to SACW of 1899 Sep 30
      - Correspondence, 1900 Jan-Apr (Box 10, Folder 213-215)
      - Correspondence, 1900 May-Dec (Box 11, Folder 216-219)
      - Correspondence, 1901 (Box 11, Folder 220-227)
      - Correspondence, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 228-231)
      - Correspondence, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 232-237)
      - Correspondence, 1904 (Box 11, Folder 238-240)
      - Correspondence to 40 Dearborn Street (Box 11, Folder 241)
        George Wilbur worked at this address in 1870, possibly in 1871 and before 1870
      - Correspondence to Champaign University (Box 11, Folder 242)
        George W. Wilbur attended Champaign University from 1872-73, and possibly before this time
      - Correspondence to 80 LaSalle Street (Box 12, Folder 243)
        George W. Wilbur worked at this address from 1878 to 1880
      - Correspondence to 99 Randolph Street (Box 12, Folder 244)
        George W. Wilbur worked here from 1881 to 1882, and from 1884 to 1886
      - Correspondence to 23 and 63 Borden Block (Box 12, Folder 245)
      - Correspondence at 89 Randolph Street (Box 12, Folder 246-247)
      - Correspondence to miscellaneous addresses (Box 12, Folder 248)
        124 Clark Street 79 Dearborn Street 95 Fifth Avenue 63 Metropolitan Block Geneva Lake, Wisconsin
      - Correspondence to or from unknown addresses (Box 12, Folder 249-251)
        Letter of [Sep] at bottom of letter from AHW in Lathrop, CA to SACW of [Sep 1]
    - Correspondence with Albert H. Wilbur
      - For Albert H. Wilbur's other correspondence, see: folders 421-474, 566c, 581
      - Correspondence, 1872 (Box 12, Folder 252)
      - Correspondence, 1873-74 (Box 12, Folder 253)
      - Correspondence, 1875 (Box 12, Folder 254-256)
        Related Archival Materials note
        See also: Letter dated [1875? Feb 13] in Box 1, folder 3
      - Correspondence, 1876 (Box 12, Folder 257-259)
      - Correspondence, 1877 (Box 12, Folder 260)
      - Correspondence, 1878 (Box 12, Folder 261)
      - Correspondence, 1879 (Box 13, Folder 262-264)
        See also: Letter dated 1879 Oct 27 in Box 3, folder 45
      - Correspondence, 1880 (Box 13, Folder 265-268)
      - Correspondence, 1881 (Box 13, Folder 269-271)
        See also: Letter dated 1881 Jan 24 in Box 4, folder 59
      - Correspondence, 1882 (Box 13, Folder 272-275)
      - Correspondence, 1883 (Box 13, Folder 276)
      - Correspondence, 1884 (Box 13, Folder 277-278)
      - Correspondence, 1885 (Box 13, Folder 279-280)
      - Correspondence, 1886-87 (Box 13, Folder 281-282)
      - Correspondence, 1889-91 (Box 14, Folder 283)
      - Correspondence, 1892-95 (Box 14, Folder 284)
      - Correspondence, 1896 (Box 14, Folder 285-288)
      - Correspondence, 1897 (Box 14, Folder 289-290)
      - Correspondence, 1898-99 (Box 14, Folder 291-292)
      - Correspondence, 1900 (Box 14, Folder 293-294)
        Letter dated Aug 20 addressed to "Mother and George"
      - Correspondence, 1901 (Box 14, Folder 295-296)
      - Correspondence, 1902 (Box 14, Folder 297-298)
      - Correspondence, 1907 (Box 14, Folder 299)
      - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 300-301)
      - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 302-305)
      - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 306-309)
      - Correspondence, 1927 Jan-May (Box 14, Folder 310-312)
      - Correspondence, 1927 Jun-Dec (Box 15, Folder 313-315)
      - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 316-318)
      - Letters from Carson City, Nevada, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 319)
        Albert lived in Carson City from 1875 to 1876
      - Letters from Reno, Nevada, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 320)
        Letter of Aug 17 addressed to "Mother & Bro." Albert lived in Reno from 1876 to 1879
      - Letters from Suisun, California, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 321)
        Albert lived in Suisun from 1883 to 1887
      - Letters from San Francisco, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 322)
        Albert lived in San Francisco from 1897 to 1902 and probably later, and in the late 1920s-early 1930s. He also passed through San Francisco at various times
      - Letters from miscellaneous addresses, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 323)
        Belvidere, Illinois Los Angeles, California Ogden, Utah Territory Owls Head, Maine Unknown
    - Correspondence with Ellen Rice Wilbur
      - For Ellen Rice Wilbur's other correspondence, see: folders 475-476, 552, 566c-580
      - Correspondence, 1875-85 (Box 15, Folder 324)
      - Correspondence, 1887 (Box 15, Folder 325)
      - Correspondence, 1888-89 (Box 15, Folder 326)
      - Correspondence, 1890 (Box 15, Folder 327)
      - Correspondence, 1891 (Box 15, Folder 327a-327b)
      - Correspondence, 1896-97 (Box 15, Folder 328-329)
        Letter of 1896 Jul 25 from SWJ to GWW at end of letter from ERW
      - Correspondence, 1898-99 (Box 15, Folder 330-331)
      - Correspondence, 1900-01 (Box 15, Folder 332)
      - Correspondence, 1903 (Box 15a, Folder 332a-332b)
      - Correspondence, 1904-05 (Box 15a, Folder 332c)
      - Correspondence, 1906 (Box 15a, Folder 332)
      - Correspondence, 1908 (Box 15a, Folder 332e)
      - Correspondence, 1909 (Box 15a, Folder 333)
      - Correspondence, 1910 (Box 15a, Folder 334-335)
      - Correspondence, 1911-12 (Box 15a, Folder 336-337)
      - Correspondence, 1913-14 (Box 16, Folder 338-339)
      - Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 340)
    - Correspondence with Susan Wilbur Jones
      - For Susan Wilbur Jones' other correspondence see: folders 488-493, 552-566b
      - Correspondence, 1896-99 (Box 16, Folder 341)
        See also: Letter dated 1896 Jul 25 in Box 15, folder 329
      - Correspondence, 1900 (Box 16, Folder 342-343)
      - Correspondence, 1901 (Box 16, Folder 344)
      - Correspondence, 1903 (Box 16, Folder 345-346)
      - Correspondence, 1905-06 (Box 16, Folder 347)
      - Correspondence, 1908 (Box 16, Folder 348)
      - Correspondence, 1909 (Box 16, Folder 349-350)
      - Correspondence, 1910 (Box 16, Folder 351-353)
      - Correspondence, 1911 (Box 16, Folder 354-358)
      - Correspondence, 1912 (Box 17, Folder 359-361)
      - Correspondence, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 362-364)
      - Correspondence, 1917-25 (Box 17, Folder 365)
      - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 366-367)
      - Correspondence, 1928-[30] (Box 17, Folder 368)
      - Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 369)
    - Correspondence with Laura Bofinger Wilbur
      - For Laura Bofinger Wilbur's other correspondence, see: folders 477-487
      - Correspondence, 1896-97 (Box 17, Folder 370)
      - Correspondence, 1898-99 (Box 17, Folder 371)
      - Correspondence, 1901-27, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 372)
    - Correspondence with Susan W. Rice
      - For Susan W. Rice's other correspondence, see: folders 494, 553, 567, 582-585a
      - Correspondence, 1883-88 (Box 17, Folder 373)
        See also: Letter dated [1885 Mar 25], Box 7, folder 116
      - Correspondence, 1899-1913, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 374)
    - Correspondence with Albert and Carrie Cook Gale
      - For Albert and Carrie Cook Gale's other correspondence, see: folders 495-503
      - Correspondence, 1886 (Box 17, Folder 375)
      - Correspondence, 1887 (Box 17, Folder 376)
      - Correspondence, 1888-90, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 377)
    - Correspondence with Others
      - Correspondence, 1867-71 (Box 17, Folder 378)
      - Correspondence, 1872 (Box 17, Folder 379)
      - Correspondence, 1873 (Box 17, Folder 380-382)
      - Correspondence, 1874 (Box 18, Folder 383-385)
      - Correspondence, 1875 (Box 18, Folder 386-387)
      - Correspondence, 1876 (Box 18, Folder 388)
      - Correspondence, 1877 (Box 18, Folder 389-391)
      - Correspondence, 1878-79 (Box 18, Folder 392)
      - Correspondence, 1880-83 (Box 18, Folder 393)
        See also: Letter dated [1882 Aug] in Box 5, folder 75
      - Correspondence, 1885-87 (Box 18, Folder 394)
      - Correspondence, 1890-91 (Box 18, Folder 395)
      - Correspondence, 1897-98 (Box 18, Folder 396)
      - Correspondence, 1899 (Box 18, Folder 397)
      - Correspondence, 1900-01 (Box 18, Folder 398)
      - Correspondence, 1902-06 (Box 18, Folder 399)
      - Correspondence, 1909-[18] (Box 18, Folder 400)
      - Correspondence, 1922-25 (Box 18, Folder 401)
      - Correspondence, 1926-[31] (Box 18, Folder 402)
      - Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 403)
    - Invitations and Christmas Cards
      - Invitations, 1874-76 (Box 19, Folder 404)
      - Invitations, 1877 (Box 19, Folder 405)
      - Invitations, 1878 (Box 19, Folder 406)
      - Invitations, 1880 (Box 19, Folder 407)
      - Invitations, 1881 (Box 19, Folder 408)
      - Invitations, 1882 (Box 19, Folder 409)
      - Invitations, 1883-84 (Box 19, Folder 410)
      - Invitations, 1885 (Box 19, Folder 411-412)
      - Invitations, 1886-91 (Box 19, Folder 413)
      - Invitations, [1903]-12 (Box 19, Folder 413a)
      - Invitations, 1913 (Box 19, Folder 414)
      - Invitations, 1914 (Box 19a, Folder 415)
      - Invitations, 1915 (Box 19a, Folder 416)
      - Invitations, 1916 (Box 19a, Folder 417)
      - Invitations, 1919 (Box 19a, Folder 417a)
      - Invitations, 1920 (Box 19a, Folder 417b)
      - Invitations, 1921 (Box 19a, Folder 417c)
      - Invitations, 1922 (Box 19a, Folder 417)
      - Invitations, n.d. (Box 19a, Folder 418-419)
      - Christmas cards, 1877-1927, n.d. (Box 19a, Folder 420)
  - WILBUR, SARAH ANN COOK
    - For Sarah Ann Cook Wilbur's other correspondence, see: folders 1-251
    - Correspondence with Albert H. Wilbur
      - For Albert H. Wilbur's other correspondence, see: folders 252-323, 566c, 581
      - Correspondence, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 421-422)
        See also: Letter of [1875 Sep] in Box 1, folder 10, and 2 letters of [1876 Jan] in Box 1, folder 12
      - Correspondence, 1876 (Box 20, Folder 423-426)
      - Correspondence, 1877 (Box 20, Folder 427)
        See also: Letter of [1877? Dec 14] in Box 2, folder 24
      - Correspondence, 1878 (Box 20, Folder 428-429)
      - Correspondence, 1879 (Box 20, Folder 430-431)
        See also: Letter of [1879 Aug] in Box 3, folder 42, and letter of 1879 Dec 9 in Box 3, folder 46
      - Correspondence, 1880 (Box 20, Folder 432-434)
        See also: Letter of 1880 Mar 8 in Box 3, folder 48
      - Correspondence, 1881 (Box 20, Folder 435-436)
      - Correspondence, 1882 (Box 21, Folder 437-438)
      - Correspondence, 1883 (Box 21, Folder 439-440)
      - Correspondence, 1884 (Box 21, Folder 441-443)
      - Correspondence, 1885 (Box 21, Folder 444-445)
        See also: Letter of 1885 Dec 13 in Box 7, folder 132
      - Correspondence, 1886 (Box 21, Folder 446-447)
        See also: Letter of 1886 Jan 27 in Box 7, folder 133
      - Correspondence, 1887 (Box 21, Folder 448-449)
      - Correspondence, 1888 (Box 21, Folder 450-451)
      - Correspondence, 1889 (Box 21, Folder 452-453)
      - Correspondence, 1890 (Box 21, Folder 454)
        See also: Letter of [1890] Jun 13 in Box 9, folder 163
      - Correspondence, 1891 (Box 21, Folder 455-456)
      - Correspondence, 1892 (Box 21, Folder 457)
      - Correspondence, 1893 (Box 21, Folder 458)
      - Correspondence, 1894 (Box 21, Folder 459)
      - Correspondence, 1895 (Box 21, Folder 460)
      - Correspondence, 1896-97 (Box 21, Folder 461)
      - Correspondence, 1898-99 (Box 21, Folder 462)
        Letter of [1898 Oct 16] on back of letter from LBW to SACW of same date
      - Correspondence, 1900 (Box 21, Folder 463)
        See also: Letter of 1900 Aug 20 in Box 14, folder 294
      - Correspondence, 1901 (Box 21, Folder 464)
      - Correspondence, 1902 (Box 21, Folder 465)
      - Correspondence, 1903-04 (Box 21, Folder 466)
      - Correspondence from Reno, Nevada (Box 22, Folder 467-468)
        See also: Letter of Aug 17 in Box 15, folder 320
        Albert lived in Reno from 1876 to 1879
      - Correspondence from Bodie, California (Box 22, Folder 469)
        Albert lived in Bodie 1879-1880
      - Correspondence from Lathrop, California (Box 22, Folder 470)
        See also: Letter of [Sep] in Box 12, folder 250.
        Albert lived in Lathrop 1881-1883
      - Correspondence from Suisun, California (Box 22, Folder 471)
        Albert lived in Suisun 1883-1887
      - Correspondence from San Francisco (Box 22, Folder 472)
        Albert lived in San Francisco from 1897 until at least 1902 and probably later, and again in the late 1920s- early 1930s. He also passed through San Francisco at various times
      - Correspondence from miscellaneous addresses (Box 22, Folder 473)
        Cheyenne, Wyoming Territory Chicago, Illinois Omaha, Nebraska Pomona, California Red Bluff, California Toano, Nevada Tucson, Arizona Territory Wells, Nevada Winnemucca, Nevada
      - Correspondence from unknown addresses (Box 22, Folder 474)
    - Correspondence with Ellen Rice Wilbur
      - For Ellen Rice Wilbur's other correspondence, see: folders 324-340, 552, 566c-580
      - Correspondence, 1890-95 (Box 22, Folder 475)
      - Correspondence, 1897-1904 (Box 22, Folder 476)
        Letter to SWJ from SACW in letter of 1897 Feb 8
    - Correspondence with Laura Bofinger Wilbur
      - For Laura Bofinger Wilbur's other correspondence, see: folders 370-372
      - Correspondence, 1891-94 (Box 22, Folder 477)
      - Correspondence, 1895 (Box 22, Folder 478-479)
      - Correspondence, 1896-98 (Box 22, Folder 480)
        See also: Letter of [1898 Oct 16] in Box 21, folder 462
      - Correspondence, 1899 (Box 22, Folder 481-482)
      - Correspondence, 1900 (Box 22, Folder 483)
      - Correspondence, 1901 (Box 22, Folder 484)
      - Correspondence, 1902 (Box 22, Folder 485)
      - Correspondence, 1903-04 (Box 22, Folder 486)
      - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 487)
    - Correspondence with Susan Wilbur Jones
      - For Susan Wilbur Jones' other correspondence, see: folders 341-369, 552-566b
      - Correspondence, 1896-98 (Box 22, Folder 488)
        Letter from SACW to SWJ of 1896 May 18 with letter of same date from SACW to SWR on back.
        See also: Letter of 1897 Feb 8 in Box 22, folder 476
      - Correspondence, 1899-1900 (Box 22, Folder 489)
      - Correspondence, 1901 (Box 22, Folder 490)
      - Correspondence, 1902 (Box 22, Folder 491)
      - Correspondence, 1903 (Box 22, Folder 492)
      - Correspondence, 1904 (Box 22, Folder 493)
    - Correspondence with Susan W. Rice
      - For Susan W. Rice's other correspondence, see: folders 373-374, 553, 567, 582-585a
      - Correspondence, 1895-1904, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 494)
        See also: Letter dated 1896 May 18 in Box 22, folder 488
    - Correspondence with Albert and Carrie Cook Gale
      - For Albert and Carrie Cook Gale's other correspondence, see: folders 375-377
      - Correspondence, 1877-83 (Box 23, Folder 495)
      - Correspondence, 1884-85 (Box 23, Folder 496)
      - Correspondence, 1886-87 (Box 23, Folder 497)
      - Correspondence, 1888 (Box 23, Folder 498-499)
      - Correspondence, 1889 (Box 23, Folder 500)
      - Correspondence, 1890 (Box 23, Folder 501-502)
      - Correspondence, 1894-98, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 503)
    - Correspondence with Others
      - Correspondence, 1848-67 (Box 23, Folder 504)
      - Correspondence, 1868 (Box 23, Folder 505-506)
      - Correspondence, 1869 (Box 23, Folder 507)
      - Correspondence, 1870 (Box 23, Folder 508)
      - Correspondence, 1871-72 (Box 23, Folder 509)
      - Correspondence, 1873-74 (Box 23, Folder 510)
      - Correspondence, 1875-77 (Box 23, Folder 511)
      - Correspondence, 1879 (Box 23, Folder 512)
        Letter of [1879] Jul 25 from Henry Cook to SACW on back of letter from Charles Cook to Henry Cook and his sister of 1879 July 23. Also letter of [1879] Jul 29 from Nelson Cook to SACW on back of letter from Charles Cook to Henry Cook of 1879 Jul 13
      - Correspondence, 1880 (Box 23, Folder 513-514)
      - Correspondence, 1881 (Box 23, Folder 515-516)
      - Correspondence, 1882 (Box 24, Folder 517-521)
        See also: Letter of [1882] Sep 16 in Box 5, folder 75
      - Correspondence, 1883 (Box 24, Folder 522)